CONTACT



czyszczon.jan99@gmail.com



+48 884 933 389



www.linkedin.com/in/czyszczonj



https://github.com/joastek



Kraków

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Front-End Solutions:

- HTML5 and CSS(Sass)
- TailwindCSS, MUI, Framer-Motion, Bulma
- RWD
- JavaScript(ES6)
- Typescript
- React, Redux-Toolkit, NextJs,
- UX/UI(Figma)
- Rest API
- Testing tools (Jest, Postman)

- Databases:

 Supabase, Poctkebase, MongoDB

- SEO:

- GoogleAds
- Google Search Console

LANGUAGES

Polish : native

• English: B2

JAN CZYSZCZOŃ

PERSONAL PROFILE

Young and ambitious front-end developer eager for fresh opportunities to elevate my skills in FrontEnd. During my free time, I am dedicated to expanding my expertise and honing my skills in healthy nutrition, powerlifting, running, and delving into historical pursuits.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Otoprzychodnie

Yokan - Custom Solutions and Online Shop | May 2023 - present

- Proactively identifying and resolving software glitches to ensure seamless functionality.
- Spearheading the conceptualization and implementation of innovative design solutions.
- Fine-tuning website performance for enhanced SEO and Google Ads effectiveness.

Stack:

- HTML5, CSS (Sass), RWD , Bulma , Figma, React, NextJs, PocketBase, Google Ads.

wwprint

June 2023 - July 2023

- Crafting and advancing comprehensive code structures.
- Discerning client requirements and cultivating strong relationships.
- Creating intuitive UX/UI designs for optimal user experiences.

Stack:

- HTML5, CSS (Sass),RWD,Framer motion, React, NextJs, EmailJs, Figma

Ventilation And Air Conditioning Engineer

Adagre Sp. z o. o. | June 2022 - present

- Management of construction sites.
- Colaboration with other enginners and managers.
- Supervision of construction works.
- Preparement of technical documentation.

EDUCATION

Politechnika Krakowska im. Tadeusza Kościuszki w Krakowie

October 2019 - January 2023

 HVAC (Heating, Ventilation and Cooling) enginner- bachelor degree.

PROJECTS

WytrenowaniApp

August 2023 - present

 A custom lifestyle and fitness appliaction, to managment body weight, trainings and nutritional values consumed.

Stack:

- HTML5, CSS, Tailwind, React, NextJs, RWD, Framer motion, MUI, Redux, Reduxtoolkit, RestAPI, Supabase, Jest.

cyandev

December 2023

My personal webiste portfolio

Stack:

- HTML5, CSS (Tailwind),RWD ,Bulma , React, NextJs, ThreeJs, framer-motion

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).